I never expected
to see him like that…
Right
I mean, your boyfriend
That's what I'm saying
You'll be on
a variety show, right?
Yeah
A government-backed
reality show
that covers the homo
and hetero couples
But would it be okay
not to be real
in a reality show?
What?
Are you not gonna
tell the truth?
What do you mean?
That guy
Hey, there's something
I didn't tell you
Actually, we've been
secretly dating
I mean, a friend I met
at a shooting set
introduced him to me
"Introduced him to me"
Hey, what kind of actor
are you?
What?
You're a terrible liar
So you mean…
you just talked
to him once
at a shooting set while
working part-time
but it was wrongly
captured like a kiss
and you ended up
playing a fake couple?
I know it sounds weird
but that's all true
Shin Yoo-il
Shin Yoo-il…
I've seen him around
this neighborhood…
Yeah, he lives here
Hey!
You already visited
his house?
I told you
It's a business
relationship
So don't worry
I don't like that guy
You know those rumors
about him, huh?
He's gone through
so many scandals
I know
but it's just a business
And the guys you liked
were all trash
What?
That's why I'm worried
Shin Yoo-il, that guy
is trash